Marya Annette McQuirter Collection 141
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - NAACP Branch Notes and Others, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - The Progressive Consumer August, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Articles on Negros in Education, 1969-1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Magazines -1920s (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Negro Newspapers and Periodicals in the United States - 1943, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Books- General info/Primary Sources, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Reading - Secondary Sources, 1981-1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Washington Welfare Assn/Southeast Welfare House, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Howard M. Bell. Youth Tell Their Story, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dance Acts, 1937-1943 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - DC Statehood Party, 1971-2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Church of God/Elder Michaux, 1981-2003 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Frederick Douglass Residence (Capitol Hill), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Frederick Douglass, 1893-2003 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Frederick Douglass Residence (Cedar Hill), undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Marvin Gaye, 1984-2003 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Howard University Hospital/Freedmen's Hospital, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Latinos, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Le Droit Park, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Leisure, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Lincoln Memorial, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Lincoln Colonade and Lincoln Theater, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Bloomingdale, 1931-1940 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Brookland, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Barnett Aden Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Ralph Bunche, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Mary Ann Shadd Cary, 1867-1877 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Chain Bridge Road School, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Gen. Benjamin O Davis, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Capitol Hill, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Fifteenth St. Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - General - DC History, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Franklin Square - Emancipation, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Civil War, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - City Hall - Old, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - 19th Century Washington, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Afro American Institute for Historic Preservation and Community Development, 1981-2002 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Phase I - Misc. Notes, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Phase II Miscellaneous ( 1 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Phase II Miscellaneous ( 2 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Phase II Miscellaneous ( 3 of 3), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Blagden Alley, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 14th and U Street NW, 1986-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Alley Dwellings, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Architects/Architecture buildings/Design, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Art, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Deanwood, 1987-2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Jelly Roll Morton, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Movie Theaters General, 1921-1937 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Murals, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pauli Murray, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Music - Misc, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Nation of Islam Temple No. 4, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - North Capitol Main Street, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Novels - DC, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - O Street Market, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Parks, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - William Sidney Pittman, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - District of Columbia Poets, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Police Brutality, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Dorothy Porter, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Reconstruction - The Uncivil War by James H. Whyte, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Recorder of Deeds, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Recreation, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Willis Richardson, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Addison Surlock, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - St. Teresa of Avila Catholic Church, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Sexuality Gay New York, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Jean Toomer, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - True Reformers Hall, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sojourner Truth, 1913-1916 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - United House of Prayer, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Carter G. Woodson, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Roy DeCarava, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Civil Rights/Black Power, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Congress Heights - Misc, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Emory UMC, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Eckington, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - The Engine Company, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - First Baptist Church, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Vinegar Hill, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Emancipation, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Fort, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - The Freedmen's Bureau, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Masonic Temple/Prince Hall, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Robert McNeill, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Elizabeth Keckly, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Metropolitan AME, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Military Road School, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Kelly Miller Articles, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Mt. Vernon, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Mt. Zion, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Slavery, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - DC Map, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - DC Population Chart, 1800-1930 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Research Clippings, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Did the Black Ghetto Have a Golden Age", 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Willis Article, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - DC Public Library Documents, 1900-1940 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tidal Basin Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Affidavit, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Major Race Riots", 1865-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NAACP DC Branch Papers, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Nesbit Article, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Negro Digest, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Glory, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "Blossom Time, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Opportunity, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Simm's Blue Book", 1923 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - The Independent Article, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The New Washington, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Leisure Time, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Planning Committee Questionnaire, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - McQuirter Article, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - The New Negro, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - The Negro in Richmond, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Economic and Social Security Committee, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Boundary Civic Association, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Southeast Civic League, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Untitled Article, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Brett Beemyn Thesis, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Journal of History of Sexuality, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - P.L.A.Y., undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Silas X. Floyd, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Research Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Black History Articles and Dissertation Notes ( 1 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Black History Articles and Dissertation Notes ( 2 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Black History Articles and Dissertation Notes ( 3 of 3), undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Photograph/Maps/Ads, 1905-1950 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Recreation Articles, 1945-1948 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1904-1924 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Smithsonian Guide for Authors, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Carter G. Woodson - The Negro Professional and the Community, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - American Quarterly, 1972-03 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Maps and Photographs, 1904-1926 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - A History of Movie Presentation in the US, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Government Correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Katherine Hazzard Gordon American Core Culture, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Charles Compton - Who Reads What, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - DC Wages -1920, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Baker handbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Second National Conference on the Problem of the Negro Youth, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Black Publishing Company, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Eduard Lindeman - Youth and Leisure, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Leisure and World War II - 1939-1945, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Blacks on the Mall, 1929-1944 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Articles on Public Libraries, 1899-1903 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 3 - Lets Dance, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Drafts, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Register of Historic Plcaes Inventory - Nomination Form, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Journal of Negro Education, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Public Library Search Results, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Reading Interests and Habits of Adults, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University Microfilm, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1943-1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Scholarly Articles, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Source Info, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ford Foundation Fellowship, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Dept. of Commerce Materials, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Primary Articles on Recreation - 1920s, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - E Franklin Frazier - Colonial Study 1937 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Consumption Articles, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - HSW Recreation, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Time on their Hands, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Charles S. Johnson - The Negro in American Civilization, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Competition Articles, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - A Study of Public Recreations for Negros, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - New Negro - 1920s, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Libraries - Primary Sources, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Woodward and Lothrop, 1880-1930 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Baltimore America's 5th Largest Music Market 1946, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Stuart L. Goosman ( 1 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Stuart L. Goosman ( 2 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Louis V Kennedy Negro Peasant, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Judds - A Study of Recreation - Facilities for Negros in Manchester 1943, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lewis Lumbard Jr. " Negro Rec: A Sample Study of the 2nd Ward of Hamilton, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - DC Children, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - DC General History, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Awkward Moves: Dance Lessons from the 1940s, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Downbeat and Metronome Articles on DC, 1943-1949 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - U Street Clubs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Criticisms of Jazz and General Articles on Jazz, 1939-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Pearl E Primus and Katherine Dunham, 1943-1949 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Survey of Recreational Facilities and Needs for Negroes, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Maps, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - DC Archives Notes, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dance Research - National Archives, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Henry Jared McGuinn MA Thesis, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Latino/Black Music DC, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - National Captial Code of Etiquette, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Baker's Dozen, 1946-1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Visual Images of DC, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Joseph W. Moss MA Thesis " The Negro and Recreation in Southern West Virginia, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Magda Crowe Thesis, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Recreation - 1930s, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - DC Black Businesses, 1949-1964 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Jean Toomer - Academic Articles, 1988-2000 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - DC Bicycles, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - DC Art Exhibits, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Urban League Directory, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Paul K Edwards - The Southern Urban Negro As a Consumer, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Washington Conservatory of Music and School of Expression, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Marian Anderson, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Consumption States, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Department Store Primary Materials, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Free Blacks/Academic Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Fort Reno/Tinleytown, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Duke Ellington, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - LeDroit Park, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Washington's 28% Plus Market, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - E Franklin Frazier - Recreation and Amusement Among Negroes, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - DC Census, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Literature and Urban Spaces - Academic Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Chicago Defender, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Libraries - Primary Materials, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - DC Census - 1940 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - DC Census - 1930 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - DC Census - 1950 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - DC Census - 1960 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Pepsi Cola Archive Materials, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Ruth Stephens Gartrell Thesis, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Malcolm X Academic Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Gay/Lesbian Academic Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - DC Churches - Store Front Churches, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Recreation - South, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Church Life/Academic Articles, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Segregation/Activism Articles Dated Post - 1940s - Present, 1940-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The First Annual Conference on Adult Education and the Negro, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - National Education Outlook Among Negroes, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Magnolia Young Interview, 1995-05 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - A Survey of the Leisure Time and Recreational Life of the Negro Boy in Columbus Ohio, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Myrdal, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Robert McNeill, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Russel H. Lyons - A Study of the Needs and Facilities for Recreation among the Negroes of Louisiana, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Afro-American Newspaper History, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hard Dancing, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Play Leisure Articles, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ebony and Jet Magazines Present the 1957 Urban Negro Market for Liquors, Wines and Beers, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Howard Theatre Articles, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Black Urban History Articles, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Recreational Facilities and Negro-White Relations in Philadelphia, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Ticket Stubs/Invitations/Pamphlets, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Event Advertisement, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - For the Love of the Great Out of Doors: Black Women and Travel During the Early to Mid Twentieth Century ( 1 of 2), 1928-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - For the Love of the Great Out of Doors: Black Women and Travel During the Early to Mid Twentieth Century ( 2 of 2), 1928-1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Dissertation: Primary Material on Reading ( 1 of 2), 1922-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Dissertation: Primary Material on Reading ( 1 of 2), 1922-1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Awkward Moves ( 1 of 2), 1943-1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Awkward Moves ( 2 of 2), 1943-1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Dissertation: Oral History interviews, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Kenneth Kusmer - "African Americans in the City Since WWII", undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Joe Curtist Photographs, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - DC Visual Images -Misc, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Latinos/Negroes, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Baver Raymond and Scott M. Cunningham - Studies in the Negro Market, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - A Study of Negro-White Marriages in DC, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Francis E. Thornton "Adjustment Problem of Certain Negro Women Migrants to Harlem, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Alain Locke Papers - Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Harlem, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Migration - Primary Articles, 1925-1928 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - DC Music, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - McQuirters, 1920-1956 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Black Journals of the U.S ( 1 of 2), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Black Journals of the U.S ( 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Second Nat'l Conference on the Problems of the Negro Youth, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Carter G Woodson - The Rural Negro - Recreation and Amusement, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photos- Leisure/Beaches/Rollerskating, 1896-1933 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Old Secondary Literature on Blacks and Cities, 1934-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Joesph R. Marches - A Comparative Study of Leisure Time Activities of Delinquent Boys and Girls, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - DC Civic Associations, 1932-1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Go Go, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Technology Time and the Conversations of Modernity, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - DC Statehood, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - DC Caribbean Community, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - DC 1970s, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Eric Porter - Chapter 2 of Dissertation, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Place/Culture/Representation eds. James Duncan and David Ley, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Urban History Articles, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Downbeat 1940s Dance Articles, 1941-1948 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Articles on Culture ( 1 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Articles on Culture ( 1 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - African American Heritage Trail, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Heritage Essay/Smithsonian, 1991-2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Theorizing Cultural Heritage (1 of 2), 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Theorizing Cultural Heritage (1 of 2), 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - DC Agenda, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Government Correspondence, 1931-1938 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Local Historical Sties - Monuments and People, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Photots/Pamphlets/Magazines/Brochures, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Research Series and Roundtable, 1986-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Transportation/Trolley Art, 1934-1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - William L. Houston Family Papers, 1897-1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Style - Washington Post Article, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Guide to Resources on the Black Press, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Music and Dance Pamphlets and info ( 1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Music and Dance Pamphlets and info ( 2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Dance and Music Newspaper Articles ( 1 of 3), 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dance and Music Newspaper Articles ( 2 of 3), 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dance and Music Newspaper Articles ( 3 of 3), 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets/Brochures/Tickets/Cards (1 of 5), undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets/Brochures/Tickets/Cards (2 of 5), undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlets/Brochures/Tickets/Cards (3 of 5), undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets/Brochures/Tickets/Cards (4 of 5), undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlets/Brochures/Tickets/Cards (5 of 5), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Misc Notes - Correspondence and Newsletters, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - African American Heritage Trail, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum of Agreement, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Black Voices for Peace ( 1 of 3), 2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Black Voices for Peace (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Black Voices for Peace (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Art/Music/Culture ( 1 of 3), 1937-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Art/Music/Culture ( 2 of 3), 1937-2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Art/Music/Culture ( 3 of 3), 1937-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - MSPC, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - CARR Coalition Against Rape and Victimization, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Interview with Alton Lucas Sr., 1907-1937 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 35th Anniversary March on Washington, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Journal, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Gelman's "Showcasing Africana", 2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Tourism Pamphlets, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Tourism Pamphlets, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Tourism Pamphlets, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Public Historian, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tour and Tourism info Booklets, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Tourism Correspondence, 2002-2009 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - African American Site Survey, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - AAHSS - Recommendations for Second Phase, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - AAHS Misc., 1975-2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - AAHS Phase I Forms Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Tourism Newspaper Articles, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - AAHS Phase I Forms Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tourism Newspaper Articles, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Network to Freedom and South Western Michigan Tourist Council, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - DC Historic Preservation Plan - 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - African American Historic Site Survey - Public Relations, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - African American Historic Site Survey - Research Assistant, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - African American Historic Site - Grant Application, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - African American Historic Site - Other State City Trails, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Master Consulting Agreement, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Historic Preservation Act, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - AAHSS First Phase - 200 Lists, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Scholarly Tourism Articles, 1972-2002 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Tourism/Civil Rights/Black Battlegrounds, 1985-2005 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Budget and Endorsement Correspondence, 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Talk Story - Smithsonian Newsletter, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - DC Inventory of Historic Sites, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - African American Historic Site Survey - Community Historians, 1926-1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Fire Alarm Box Correspondence, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Thurgood Marshall Center U Street Exhibit, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Dunbar High School, 1917-1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - African American Historic Site Survey Agenda Minutes, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Researchers - Research Materials, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Forms - Grant in Aid Program, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Expenses, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - CIPS Certification Workshop Info, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - History Pamphlets (1 of 4), undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - History Pamphlets (2 of 4), undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - History Pamphlets (3 of 4), undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - History Pamphlets (4 of 4), undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Adolf Cluss Exhibition Project, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Sisterspace Correspondence, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lifting as we Climb: from Emancipation to Desegregation, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1919 Riot, 1919-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Spirit Journey: Class Assignments, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "Washington: Symbol and City", 2004 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - DC History and Politics (1 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - DC History and Politics (2 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - DC History and Politics (3 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - William H Johnson, 1973-1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - DC History Pamphlets and Ads ( 1 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - DC History Pamphlets and Ads ( 2 of 2), 1998-2005 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Magazines, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - DC Rape Crisis Center ( 1 of 2), 1972-1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - DC Rape Crisis Center ( 2 of 2), 1972-1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - African Concepts of Education ( 1 of 2), 1971-1988 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - African Concepts of Education ( 2 of 2), 1971-1988 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Vegetarianism, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - History Articles, 1992-2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Primary Documents: Correspondence and News Clippings, 1935-1946 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation Chapters ( 1 of 3), undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Dissertation Chapters ( 2 of 3), undated (Box 28, Folder 5)